<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>vegetarian on Summer QRemix</title><link>https://mipmip.github.io/summer-qremix/tags/vegetarian/</link><description>Recent content in vegetarian on Summer QRemix</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://mipmip.github.io/summer-qremix/tags/vegetarian/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Austrian vanilla crescents</title><link>https://mipmip.github.io/summer-qremix/recipe/vanilla-crescents/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mipmip.github.io/summer-qremix/recipe/vanilla-crescents/</guid><description>You can substitute almond flour for the ground walnuts.
Cut butter into ½ inch cubes, then set aside in the freezer to keep cold. Meanwhile prepare the rest of the ingredients. Weigh the flour and set aside in the freezer or fridge as well. The colder the ingredients, the better. Grind walnuts very finely with a mouli grater (I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find walnut meal). Don&amp;rsquo;t use a food processor, the chopped pieces will still come out too big.</description></item><item><title>Cauliflower steaks with roasted red pepper &amp; olive salsa</title><link>https://mipmip.github.io/summer-qremix/recipe/cauliflower-steaks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mipmip.github.io/summer-qremix/recipe/cauliflower-steaks/</guid><description>Unlock the flavours of cauliflower with a red pepper, olive and caper salsa, topped with almonds. Healthy and vegan, it makes a tasty light lunch or supper.
Heat oven to 220C/200C fan/gas 7 and line a baking tray with baking parchment. Slice the cauliflower into two 1-inch steaks – use the middle part as it’s larger, and save the rest for another time. Rub the paprika and 1⁄2 tbsp oil over the steaks and season.</description></item><item><title>Griddled halloumi with watermelon &amp; caper breadcrumbs</title><link>https://mipmip.github.io/summer-qremix/recipe/halloumi-watermelon-breadcrumbs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mipmip.github.io/summer-qremix/recipe/halloumi-watermelon-breadcrumbs/</guid><description>This salad has a great interplay of textures, temperatures and flavours. Toss juicy watermelon with salty cheese, crispy breadcrumbs, capers, almonds and mint.
Cut the watermelon into either cubes or slices and transfer to a bowl with the very finely sliced shallots. Add 4 tbsp extra virgin olive oil and the balsamic, then season with fresh black pepper. Cover and put in the fridge for about 15-20 mins. Heat the remaining oil in a frying pan.</description></item><item><title>Lime, physalis and elderflower caipiroska</title><link>https://mipmip.github.io/summer-qremix/recipe/physalis-caipiroska/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mipmip.github.io/summer-qremix/recipe/physalis-caipiroska/</guid><description>Lime, Physalis and Elderflower Caipiroska
Equipment 1 x Short Glass 1 x Crushed ice 1 x Jigger 1 x Muddler 1 x Chopping Board 1 x Knife Cut the lime in wedges, take out the white membrane, then cut the physalis in half and place in a glass. Muddle the lime, physalis with the Elderflower sugar syrup in the glass. With the muddler press down on the lime and physalis to extract flavor and juices.</description></item></channel></rss>